<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2 http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2.xsd">
 <p xlink:href="rest/p/pear2_net_transmitter">PEAR2_Net_Transmitter</p>
 <c>pear2.php.net</c>
 <v>1.0.0a2</v>
 <a>1.0.0</a>
 <mp>5.3.0</mp>
 <st>alpha</st>
 <l>LGPL License 2.1</l>
 <m>boen_robot</m>
 <s>Wrapper for network stream functionality.
</s>
 <d>PHP has built in support for various types of network streams, such as HTTP and TCP sockets. One problem that arises with them is the fact that a single fread/fwrite call might not read/write all the data you intended, regardless of whether you're in blocking mode or not. While the PHP manual offers a workaround in the form of a loop with a few variables, using it every single time you want to read/write can be tedious.

This package abstracts this away, so that when you want to get exactly N amount of bytes, you can be sure the upper levels of your app will be dealing with N bytes. Oh, and the functionality is nicely wrapped in an object (but that's just the icing on the cake).</d>
 <da>2011-10-16 00:27:19</da>
 <n>Lots of reorganization and initial test suite.

* Renamed all &quot;Socket*Transmitter&quot; classes to &quot;Tcp*&quot;.
* Added test suite with nearly complete code coverage. Remaining coverage is due to forward compatibility issues.
* Added FilterCollection, in turn allowing for the same filter to be applied more than once.
* Added NetworkStream, and made Tcp* classes inherit from it. This new class contains a new method called shutdown().
* IPv6 addresses must now be written literally, without the surrounding &quot;[&quot; and &quot;]&quot;.
* TcpServerConnection can now accept IPv6 connections.
* Merged sendStream() into send().
* Added $offset and $length to send().
* Removed redundant error variables in TcpServerConnection.
* Removed the TcpServerConnection::isServer() function (can't tell apart server and client).</n>
 <f>36118</f>
 <g>http://pear2.php.net/get/PEAR2_Net_Transmitter-1.0.0a2</g>
 <x xlink:href="package.1.0.0a2.xml"/>
</r>
